[{"question": " here you go pheebs. who else wants one of my special homemade brownies?", "answer": " i will have one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " okay, i\u0092m not gonna have one.", "answer": " neither will i.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " no, no, it\u0092s just my tooth.", "answer": " all right i\u0092ll have one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " so what\u0092s a matter, you need a dentist? i\u0092ve got a good one.", "answer": " no thanks, i have a good one too. i just, i, i can\u0092t see him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " see that is the problem with invisible dentists.", "answer": " why? why can\u0092t you go to him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " because, every time i go to the dentist, somebody dies.", "answer": " that is so weird, because every time i go to the dentist, i look down the hygienist\u0092s blouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " phoebe, what? umm...what?!", "answer": " yeah, yeah, first there was my aunt mary, and then there was umm, john, my mailman, and then my, my cowboy friend \u0091albino bob\u0092.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " and all these people actually died?", "answer": " yes, while i was in the chair! that\u0092s why i take such good care of my teeth now, y'know, it\u0092s not about oral hygiene, i floss to save lives!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " pheebs, come on, you didn\u0092t kill anybody, these people just happened to die when you went to the dentist. it\u0092s, it\u0092s, it\u0092s just ah, a coincidence.", "answer": " well tell that to them. oh! you can\u0092t, their dead. opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " thanks, gunther.   hey!  umm, can i get a napkin too?", "answer": " oh, like you don\u0092t already have everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " phoebe, your in pain, would you just go to the dentist, just go.", "answer": " all right, fine, fine, but if you\u0092re my next victim, don\u0092t come back as a poltergeist and like suck me into the tv set.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i promise.", "answer": " although, don\u0092t feel like you can\u0092t visit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  hey, is, is, is chandler here?", "answer": "  no, no he\u0092s not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " you guys, joey just saw janice kissing her ex-husband.", "answer": " what?  so what are you going to do? i mean how, how are you going to tell chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " well, i was thinking about that and i, i think the best way would be, to not.", "answer": " joey, you can\u0092t keep this to yourself, if you know about this, you have to tell him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " it\u0092ll kill him. i mean it\u0092ll, it\u0092ll just kill him.", "answer": " well, you could wait \u0091til i go to the dentist, maybe i\u0092ll kill him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  ewww! ugly naked guy is using his new hammock. it\u0092s like a play-doo fat factory.", "answer": " well, i\u0092m going to the dentist, so listen, okay, just be on the look out for anything that, that, that you can fall into, or, or that can fall on you, or... all right, just look out! okay, and um, i also just wanna, i just wanna tell you all that um......", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " okay, i have a problem i have to go into work for a few hours, some kids messed up the homo sapien display.", "answer": " what did they do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " well, they painted over the word \u0091sapien\u0092 for one thing, then they rearranged the figures, let\u0092s just leave it at that.", "answer": " so, do you want me to watch ben for you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yes, that\u0092s what i was going to ask, thank you.", "answer": " whoa! wait! hello! what about me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey-hey, ross?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i\u0092ve got a science question.", "answer": " hmm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " if the homo sapiens, were in fact \u0091homo-sapien\u0092, is that why there extinct?", "answer": " joey, homo sapiens are people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  look benny, spoon.  spoon. come on! all right, y'know what i think he\u0092s bored.", "answer": " here. ben, do you wanna play the airplane game, do you wanna show rachel? come here.  we\u0092re gonna do something fun. okay.  weee!!  weee!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  who\u0092s so brave, you\u0092re so brave, yes you are, you\u0092re so brave.", "answer": " okay. okay honey, he\u0092s fine, he\u0092s fine, let\u0092s just put him down. come here, ben.  see that\u0092s a good boy.  how could you do that to him!! ross trusted me, what is he going to say?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " he\u0092s not gonna say anything, because we\u0092re not gonna tell him.", "answer": " we\u0092re not?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no we\u0092re not.", "answer": " all right, i like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " so we\u0092re okay, we\u0092re okay, we\u0092re okay,  aren\u0092t we? no, we\u0092re not okay, we\u0092re not okay, there\u0092s a bump, there\u0092s a bump.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh my god! well push it in! push it in!", "answer": " i cannot push it in!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " okay, we\u0092re gonna need a distraction.", "answer": " okay, okay, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i got it!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " the second that ross walks in that door, i want you take him back to your bedroom and do whatever it is that you do that makes him go,  rweee!!", "answer": " or. we could put a hat on his head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " a hat! yes! we need a hat.", "answer": " we need a hat..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " where are we gonna find a tiny little hat?", "answer": " oh, oh, oh, i\u0092ll get \u0091rainy day bear\u0092!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " because he\u0092ll know what to do?  oh my god, you\u0092re a genius!", "answer": " oh god, oh god, it\u0092s sowed on though.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " give it. give it.", "answer": " okay.  monica and rachel: oh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey! hold on a minute, hold on a second. do you think these pearls are nice?", "answer": " i\u0092d really prefer a mountain bike.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " janice\u0092s birthday is coming up, i want to get her something speacial. come in here with me.", "answer": " whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, whoa. do you ah, want to get her something speacial, get her flowers, get her candy, get her gum, girls love gum.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " that\u0092s a good idea, \u0091dear janice have a hubba-bubba birthday\u0092. i would like to get her something serious.", "answer": " oh, you want something serious. y'know what you should do, you should get her one of those um, barium enemas. those are dead serious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  no, no, you can\u0092t, you can\u0092t, okay, you can\u0092t, you can\u0092t buy her pearls, you just can\u0092t, you can\u0092t, you can\u0092t.", "answer": " why not?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " oh god. uh, okay, here\u0092s the thing, this is the thing, okay, the thing is...", "answer": " what is the thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " okay. i went down to the \u0091mattress king\u0092 showroom and, and i saw janice, kissing her ex-husband.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " they were in his office.", "answer": " well she, she wouldn\u0092t do that, she\u0092s with, she\u0092s with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i\u0092m telling you man, i saw it.", "answer": " yeah, well, you\u0092re wrong! okay, you\u0092re wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " it just makes more sense as an ensemble.", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " besides, it takes the focus off the hat.", "answer": "  no! oh! you\u0092re alive! you\u0092re alive!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " see pheebs, i promised you no one would die, didn\u0092t i?", "answer": " yeah, well, we\u0092ll see about that. can i use your phone? i just wanna call everyone i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " sure, we have no money, go ahead.", "answer": "  \u0091hey! you\u0092re not dead! okay, see ya!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " monica.", "answer": " oh my god! he just said my name! did you hear that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " monica bang!", "answer": " okay, i heard that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " did he just say \u0091monica bang\u0092?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh my god! he\u0092s gonna rat me out!", "answer": " monica bang!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh-ho-ho, sweetie, sweetie, you gotta stop saying that, now. it\u0092s no big deal, it\u0092s not even worth mentioning, you see we all do it all the time. see watch this, ben, ben, ben.  ow, monica bang!  everybody bang.  ben bang.  rachel bang.  bang, rachel bang! oh, isn\u0092t that fun?", "answer": "  look at that!  look at that!  we all do it.  okay, i\u0092m stopping now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " you okay?", "answer": " oh yeah! y'know, if it\u0092s not a headboard, it\u0092s just not worth it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  how\u0092s my bing-a-ling?", "answer": " ah, i don\u0092t know, you tell me. anything you ah, wanna tell me, because, if you ah, you should, if you, you would, tell me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " why are your eyes so white?", "answer": " you tell me! maybe, it\u0092s because i was just fooling with my ex! oh no-no-no-no, no-no-no-no, that was you!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh my god!!", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " how did you know?", "answer": " joey told me, he saw you two kissing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " in the park?", "answer": " no! in his office! how many kisses were there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " just those two!", "answer": " wh-wh-why, wh-why, why, why was there kissing!? there should be no kissing!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh, i\u0092m sorry honey, i\u0092m so, so,  haaaaa! i\u0092m so, so sorry, i just  haaaaaa! but i, oh what happened was, i-i-i can\u0092t breathe. can you get me a bag, or something?", "answer": "  here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " the receipt.", "answer": " i\u0092ll take it! all right look, i gotta know. are you finished with me?  are you finished with him?  do you still love him?  do you still love me?  all right look,  i\u0092m gonna need an actual answer here okay, so which is it, him or me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know.", "answer": "  okay. if you\u0092re alive you answer your phone! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay, ben, i won\u0092t tell your daddy that you had ice cream for dinner, if you don\u0092t tell about our little bonking incident.", "answer": " monica, number one, i don\u0092t think ben understands the concept of bribery, and number two, i...   what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " you said number two.", "answer": " i also said number one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  hey! everyone.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " how\u0092s my little boy?", "answer": " he\u0092s perfect, he\u0092s never been better.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  what\u0092d you do, take him whaling?", "answer": " monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh my god, he just said your name, that\u0092s great! good job ben.", "answer": " monica bang!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh that\u0092s right, that\u0092s what i\u0092d sound like if i exploded.", "answer": " woo-hoo! the curse is broken! i called everybody i know, and everyone is alive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " uh.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh my god! i killed him! i killed another one! and this curse is getting stronger too, to bring down something that big.", "answer": " well maybe he\u0092s just taking a nap.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i\u0092m tellin\u0092 ya, he hasn\u0092t moved since this morning.", "answer": " all right, we should call somebody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " and tell them what? the naked guy we stare at all the time isn\u0092t moving.", "answer": " well, we have gotta find out if he\u0092s alive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " how are we gonna do that? there\u0092s no way.", "answer": " well, there is one way. his window\u0092s open, i say, we poke him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " hey! y'know how we ah, save all those chopsticks for no reason we get when we get chinese food?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " well, now we got a reason.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " well, we\u0092re fashioning a very long poking device.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey uh, what\u0092s a matter?", "answer": " i talked to janice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oh my god, is she going back to him?", "answer": " she doesn\u0092t know. says she loves us both. y'know i woke up this morning and i was in love, well i was happy. y'know it serves me right for buying that twelve pack of condoms. and now i can\u0092t even return them, because she choked on the reciept!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " what are you ah, what are you gonna do?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, y'know. what, what, would you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " well, it doesn\u0092t matter what i would do.", "answer": " come on, tell me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " all right, you\u0092re probably not gonna want to hear this but ah, if it was me, and this is just me,  i would ah, i would bow out.", "answer": " what?  what are you, what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, he\u0092s finally alseep. about that ah, bump on his head?", "answer": " are you, are you, are you sure it\u0092s ah, a new bump? i mean, no offense, i\u0092ve always thought of ben as a fairly bumpy headed child.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " it\u0092s okay if he bumps his head, kids bump their heads all the time, y'know, it was your first time babysitting, i figured you did the best you could.", "answer": "  i did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i know! i\u0092m saying you have to watch them all the time.", "answer": " i did!! i watched! i watched! i watched monica bang his head against that thing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " monica?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " umm, did you notice anything wierd about ben today?", "answer": " no. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " well, i was just playing with him, and y'know we were doing the alphabet song, which he used to be really good at, but suddenly he\u0092s leaving out \u0091e\u0092 and \u0091f.\u0092 it\u0092s like they just ah, i don\u0092t know, fell out of his head.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i hope it\u0092s still funny when you\u0092re in hell.", "answer": "  you jerk! you know how much i love that kid!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " monica bang! monica bang!  ow!", "answer": " i\u0092ll get the hat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " janice, i have something i need to tell you, and i want you to let me get through it, because it\u0092s, it\u0092s, it\u0092s not gonna be easy.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " i think you should go back with gary. i don\u0092t wanna be the guy that breaks up a family, y'know when my parents split up, it was because of that guy. whenever i would see him i was always think y'know \u0091you\u0092re the reason, you are the reason why their not together.\u0092 and i hated that guy. and it didn\u0092t matter how nice he was, or how happy he made my dad.", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " yeah, well. it\u0092s the right thing to do.", "answer": " oh! you\u0092re right. oh god. but, before i can say \u0091good-bye\u0092, there\u0092s something i really need you to know, chandler. the way i feel about you, it\u0092s like, i finally understand what lionel richie\u0092s been singing about. y'know, i mean what we have, it\u0092s like movie love, you\u0092re my soulmate, and i can\u0092t believe we\u0092re not going to be spending the rest of our lives together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " then don\u0092t leave me!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " forget what i said, i was babbling! pick me!", "answer": " no, you were right, you were right. i mean, i-i-i\u0092ve got to give my marriage another chance.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " no you don\u0092t! no, no, no, i say you have to give your divorce another chance.", "answer": "  i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " ohhh. don\u0092t go.", "answer": " no, i-i-i gotta go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no. no! no! no!", "answer": " honey, honey, people are looking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " i don\u0092t care!  i don\u0092t care!!", "answer": " yeah, um, i\u0092m, i\u0092m leaving now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " you can\u0092t leave! i have your shoe!", "answer": " good-bye chandler bing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " all right now remember, something this big and long is going to be difficult to manuver, fortunately i have a lot of experience in that area.", "answer": " can we please focus here, a naked man\u0092s life hangs in the balance!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i\u0092m telling you he\u0092s dead. what we are about to have here is a dead fat guy on a stick.", "answer": " all right, ladies and gentlemen, let\u0092s poke.  steady. steady. okay, a little higher. careful of the angle. okay, okay, we\u0092re approaching the window  thread the needle. thread the needle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " he\u0092s alive! he\u0092s a-live!!!", "answer": " and yet, we\u0092re still poking him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " okay, retract the device, retract the device.", "answer": " he does not look happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hey-hey, now he\u0092s showing us his poking device.", "answer": " hey, that\u0092s never gonna make it all the way over here, buddy! closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  \u0091i\u0092ll hold you close in my arms.  i can\u0092t resist your charms. and love....\u0092", "answer": "  \u0091love....\u0092 chandler and phoebe: \u0091i\u0092ll be a fool for you. i\u0092m sure, you know i don\u0092t mind.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  \u0091no you know i don\u0092t mind.\u0092 chandler and phoebe: \u0091yes! you mean the world the world to me. oh..\u0092", "answer": " \u0091i know.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " \u0091i know.\u0092", "answer": " \u0091i\u0092ve found.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}]